<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.drawy</id>
  <name>Drawy</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">السبورة</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Drawy</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Drawy</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Drawy</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Drawy</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Drawy</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">Drawy</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Drawy</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">Drawy</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Drawy</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Drawy</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Drawy</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Drawy</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Drawy</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Drawy</name>
  <summary>Your handy, infinite, brainstorming tool</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">أداة مفيدة غير محدودة لتبادل الأفكار</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">La vostra eina pràctica, infinita i de pluja d'idees</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">La vostra eina pràctica, infinita i de pluja d'idees</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Ihr unbegrenzt nützliches Werkzeug zur Ideenfindung</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Herramienta práctica e infinita para generar lluvia de ideas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Zure ideia-jasa tresna erabilgarri eta infinitua</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">כלי סיעור המוחין השימושי והאינסופי שלך</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Il tuo pratico e infinito strumento di brainstorming</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">თქვენი მოსახერხებელი, უსასრულო განსჯის ხელსაწყო</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Uw handige, oneindige hulpmiddel voor brainstormen!</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Sua ferramenta prática e infinita para brainstorming</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Vaše priročno, neskončno orodje za viharjenje možgan</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Kullanışlı, sınırsız beyin fırtınası aracın</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Ваша зручна, нескінченна програма для мозкових штурмів</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">好用的無限畫布腦力激盪工具</summary>
  <developer id="org.kde.drawy">
    <name>Prayag Jain</name>
  </developer>
  <metadata_license>CC-BY-4.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <description>
    <p>Drawy is a work-in-progress infinite whiteboard tool, which aims to be a native desktop alternative to the amazing web-based Excalidraw.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">السبورة  هي أداة لوحة بيضاء لا نهائية لا تزال تحت التطوير، وتهدف إلى أن تكون بديلاً أصلياً لبرنامج Excalidraw الرائع القائم على الويب.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Drawy és una eina de pissarra infinita en desenvolupament, que pretén ser una alternativa nativa d'escriptori a l'increïble Excalidraw basat en web.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Drawy és una eina de pissarra infinita en desenvolupament, que pretén ser una alternativa nativa d'escriptori a l'increïble Excalidraw basat en web.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Drawy ist ein in Entwicklung befindliches Whiteboard-Werkzeug mit unendlicher Zeichenfläche. Ziel ist, eine für den Desktop optimierte Alternative zum fantastischen webbasierten Excalidraw zu bieten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Drawy es una herramienta de pizarra infinita en desarrollo, que pretende ser una alternativa nativa de escritorio a la increíble herramienta web Excalidraw.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Drawy garapen fasean dagoen arbela mugagabeko tresna bat da, web oinarriko Excalidraw tresna bikainaren mahaigaineko alternatiba natiboa izatea helburu duena.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">Drawy הוא כלי לוח רעיונות אינסופי שעדיין נמצא בפיתוח, מטרתו היא לספק חלופה טבעית לשולחן העבודה לכלי המקוון המדהים Excalidraw.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Drawy è una lavagna infinita in fase di sviluppo, che si propone di essere un'alternativa desktop nativa allo straordinario Excalidraw basato sul web.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">Drawy ჯერ კიდევ შემუშავების ქვეშ მყოფი უსასრულო დაფაა, რომელიც აპირებს, ვებზე დაფუძნებული Excalidraw-ის ალტერნატივას წარმოადგენდეს.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Drawy is een oneindig whiteboardprogramma in ontwikkeling, dat een inheems bureaubladalternatief wil zijn voor het fantastische webgebaseerde Excalidraw.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Drawy é uma ferramenta de quadro branco infinito em desenvolvimento, que pretende ser uma alternativa nativa para desktop ao incrível Excalidraw, baseado na web.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Drawy je orodje v razvoju za neskončno tablo, ki naj bi postalo izvorna namizna alternativa neverjetnemu spletnemu programu Excalidraw.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Drawy, harika web tabanlı Excalidraw’a yerel bir masaüstü alternatifi olmayı hedefleyen, geliştirme aşamasında bir sınırsız beyaz tahta aracıdır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Drawy динамічна нескінченна дошка, яка має стати альтернативою чудової мережевої Excalidraw для робочих станцій.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">Drawy 是一個開發中的無限白板工具，希望成為網路上好用的 Excalidraw 的原生桌面替代品。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://invent.kde.org/prayag/drawy</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://invent.kde.org/prayag/drawy/issues</url>
  <url type="vcs-browser">https://invent.kde.org/prayag/drawy</url>
  <url type="contribute">https://invent.kde.org/prayag/drawy</url>
  <categories>
    <category>Qt</category>
    <category>Graphics</category>
  </categories>
  <recommends>
    <control>pointing</control>
  </recommends>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">moderate</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">moderate</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
  <provides>
    <binary>drawy</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.drawy.desktop</launchable>
  <branding>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="light">#27a9ff</color>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="dark">#002d6c</color>
  </branding>
</component>
